A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Vice President for Administration, Stuart K. Cassell, 1945-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- 1971
  - Computer Science Applications Program Proposal, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Proposal to Consolidate Bachelor's Program in Education, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - University Council Meeting, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Proposal for New Curriculum in the College of Engineering, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Proposal to Consolidate Master Degree Programs, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - University Council Minutes, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Proposed Doctor of Philosophy with degree in Sociology, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Commission for Student Affairs, Minutes, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, Meeting Minutes, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - University Council Minutes, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Proposal of Doctor of Education (3 folders), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 29-31)
  - University Council Minutes (3 folders), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 33-34, Box 45, Folder 1)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprise, including Airport and Air Show (2 folders), 1971 (Box 68, Folder 12-13)
- 1972
  - University Council Possible Changes (3 folders), 1972 (Box 45, Folder 8-10)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Traffic Committee, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Meeting of Public Relations Committee and Athletic Association, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Ad Hoc Committee Complimentary Tickets, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Senate, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Building Committee, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Committee, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - T. Marshall Hahn Jr. (7 folders), 1972 (Box 45, Folder 21-25, Box 46, Folder 1-2)
  - Brown, J. Gordon- Dean of Student Services, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Bull, Fred W., Graduate School, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Burchard, Charles- Architecture, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Dean, James W. (4 folders), 1972 (Box 46, Folder 6-9)
  - Harvard, William C., Arts and Sciences, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Hereford, Karl T.- Education, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Hill, David E.- Dean Student Programs, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Lacy, M.P., Admissions and Records, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Lavery, W.E., Vice President-Finance, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - McKeefery, W.J., Vice President-Executive, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Martin, J.E., Agriculture, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Malpass, L.F., Vice President-Academic Affairs, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Mitchell, H.H.-Business, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Moseley, F.O.- Athletic Director, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Ryland, W.H., General Counsel, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Robertson- Research, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Skelton, W.E. Extension, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Torgersen, Paul E.-Engineering, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Bell, W.B.- University Development, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Boone, J.F.- Treasurer, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Burke, C.E.- Comptroller, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Butt, A.T.- Personnel, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cato, W.H., Placement, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Colby, Chuck- Administration Intern, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Evans, E.B., Business Manager, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Heterick, R.C., Computing Center, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - King, H.P., Food Services, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Montgomery, J.R., Institutional Research, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Nickols, I.E., Security, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Rudolph, G.A., Library, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Russell, G.E., Alumni Office, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Shotts, J.L., Purchasing, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Schiffert, C.W.- Infirmary, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Sterrett, W.M., Buildings and Grounds, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C., Physical Plant Planning, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Strother, W.H., Information Services (2 folders), 1972 (Box 47, Folder 15-16)
  - Wheeler, R.- Housing, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - The Art Commission, Floyd E. Johnson, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Attorney General, Andrew P. Miller, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, Joseph F. James, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, H.D.Hamner, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Governor, A. Linwood Holton, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Division of Budget, John R. McCutcheon, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Division of Personnel, John W. Garber, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Department of Property Records and Insurance-Stewart R. Moore, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Department of Purchases and Supplies, B.P Alsop Jr., 1972 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Department of Treasury, Walter W. Craigie, Jr., 1972 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - State Highway Department, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - A-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Appalachian Electric Power Company (2 folders), 1972 (Box 47, Folder 31-32)
  - Applications, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Blacksburg, Town of, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Blanket Letters, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Budget-Miscellaneous Items, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Building Dedications, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Capital Outlay-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Cassell, S.K.- Personal (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Centennial- G.W. Litton (4 folders), 1972 (Box 48, Folder 12-15)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Crawford, A.W.- Business Manager Squires, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Disruptive Activities, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Department of Biochemistry, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Electrical Distribution-Wiley and Wilson (2 folders), 1972 (Box 48, Folder 22-23)
  - Equal Employment Opportunities-Civil Rights (2 folders), 1972 (Box 48, Folder 24-25)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Fireworks Display, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - First National Bank Exchange, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Governor's Management Study, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard, Inc (3 folders), 1972 (Box 48, Folder 35-37)
  - Military-General Henderson and Others, 1972 (Box 48, Folder 38)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Land Grant Meeting, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Motor Pool Operations, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - NASULGC- Council for Business Affairs, Executive Committee, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - K-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Mc-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - National Association of Colleges and University Business Officers, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - NCH Corporation, Lacy McClain (2 folders), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 12-13)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Orientation, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Overtime-Authorized, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Payne, Alfred C., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Physical Examinations, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - Research Park, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - Reston, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - SACUBO, Southern Association of College and Universities Business Officers (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - Scholarships, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Statement of Expenditures and Balances, 1972-01-31-1972-12-31 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  - Student Aid Association (2 folders), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 27-28)
  - Student Correspondence, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  - Student Government Association- General, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  - Task Force for Innovation in Instruction, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 32)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Unemployment Act, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  - VPI Facilities Inc, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Tech Union, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  - Water Authority (3 folders), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 38-40)
  - University Council (6 folders), 1972 (Box 45, Folder 2-7)
  - Financial Statements (2 folders), 1972 (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
  - University Council Meeting Minutes, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Education Placement Report, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Placement Services-Annual Report, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Unaudited Financial Statements (2 folders), 1972 (Box 56, Folder 12-13)
  - University Services and Auxiliary Enterprise, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- 1973
  - Doctor of Philosophy in Computer Science and Applications Proposal, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - University Council Agenda, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Doctor of Philosophy Proposal, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - University Council, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - University Council Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Doctorate of Philosophy in Psychology, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - University Council Meeting, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - University Council Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for Bachelor of Arts in Geography, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - University Council Meeting Minutes (8 folders), 1973 (Box 50, Folder 13-20)
  - Building Committee, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Committee (2 folders), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Commission on Student Affairs (2 folders), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
  - Faculty Senate, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Traffic Committee, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall, Jr. (12 folders), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10-21)
  - Brown, J. Gordon, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Bull, F.W., 1973 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Burchard, Charles, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Dean, James W. (4 folders), 1973 (Box 51, Folder 25-26, Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Harper, Laura Jane, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Harvard, W.C., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Hereford, K.C., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Hill, D.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Lacy, M.P., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Lavery, W.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - McKeefery, W.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Malpass, L.F. (2 folders), 1973 (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
  - Martin, J.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, H.H., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Robertson, R.M., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Ryland, W.H., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Skelton, W.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Torgersen, P.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Bell,W.B., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Boone, J.F., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Burke, C.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Butt, A.T. (2 folders), 1973 (Box 52, Folder 21-22)
  - Colby, Chuck- Administration Intern, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Evans, E.B., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Hanau, D.O., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Heterick, R.C., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - King, H.P., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Montgomery, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Moseley, F.O., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Nickols, I.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Nunley, C.F., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Rudolph, G.A., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Russell, G.E., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Schiffert, C.W., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Shotts, J.L., 1973 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Sterrett, W.M. (2 folders), 1973 (Box 52, Folder 36-37)
  - Strother, W.H. (2 folders), 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
  - Wheeler, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - The Art Commission, Floyd E. Johnson, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Attorney General, Andrew P. Miller, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Division of Budget-John R. McCutcheon, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Division of Personnel, John W. Garber, Jr., 1973 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Property Records and Insurance, Stewart R. Moore, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, J.D. Hamner Jr., 1973 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Purchases and Supply, B.P. Alsop, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Department of Treasury, W.W. Craigie Jr., 1973 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Governor Linwood Holton, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - State Council of Higher Education (2 folders), 1973 (Box 53, Folder 13-14)
  - State Highway Department, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - A-Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Small Animal Holding Facilities, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Appalachian Power Company, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Applications, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Blacksburg- Town of, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Blanket Letters, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Budget Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Building Dedications, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Building Lock-Up, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - C-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Capital Outlay-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Cassell,S.K.-Personal, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Copying Services Committee, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Crawford, A.W.-Business Manager Squires, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - E-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Equal Opportunity Employment, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Fireworks Display, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - First National Bank Exchange, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Founders Day Program Committee, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Health, Education, Welfare Department, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Handbook, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - K-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Krebs, A.H. (2 folders), 1973 (Box 54, Folder 7-8)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Lane, E.H. Sr.-Memorial, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Chas. Lunsford Sons and Izard (3 folders), 1973 (Box 54, Folder 11-13)
  - Long Term Disability Insurance, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield-Southwest Virginia, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Mc-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Eva C. McDonald-Hearing, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Military-General Henderson, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Motor Pool Operations (2 folders), 1973 (Box 54, Folder 20-21)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - NACUBO (2 folders), 1973 (Box 54, Folder 23-24)
  - NASULGC-Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - NCH Corporation, Lacy McLain, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - National Science Foundation, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Orientation, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Organization Charts, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - Overtime Authorized, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Payne, Alfred C., 1973 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Physical Examinations, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - Reston, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Research Park, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Retirement, VA Supplemental (2 folders), 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Pre Graduation Interview Report (2 folders), 1973 (Box 55, Folder 4-5)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Sanitation Authority, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - SACUBO, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Scholarships, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Student Correspondence, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Student Aid Correspondence, H.H. McEver (2 folders), 1973 (Box 55, Folder 11-12)
  - Student Government Association, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - TRW Property, VPI Educational Foundation, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Lease-Tobacco Acreage, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - John Ferguson, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Leases-Land Rentals, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - TRW, Inc, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Solid Waste Disposal Study, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - VPI Facilities, Inc, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Water Authority, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Wyatt Memorial Fund, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Placement Services, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Financial Statements (4 folders), 1973 (Box 55, Folder 30-31, Box 56, Box-folder 1-2)
  - Nuclear Reactor Research Proposal (2 folders), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 5-6)
  - Placement Services Annual Report-1972-1973, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - School of Medicine Proposal-UNC Chapel Hill, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - First National Exchange Bank-Trust Division, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Pre Graduation Interview Report, 1972-1973, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Short Range Traffic and Parking Improvements, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Terminal Interview Report, 1972-1973 (2 folders), 1973 (Box 56, Folder 16-17)
  - Swink, H.W., 1973 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- 1974
  - Curriculum Manual-Annual Report, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Pre Graduation Interview Report-Cover Letter, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Proposed Degree in Doctor of Philosophy, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - University Council Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Proposed Doctor of Environmental Planning and Design (3 folders), 1974 (Box 56, Folder 20-22)
  - University Council, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - University Council Meeting, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - University Council Meeting Minutes (5 folders), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 1-5)
  - Athletic and Ticket Promotion (2 folders), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Building Committee, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Committee, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Commission on Student Affairs, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Senate, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Search Committee for President, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Traffic Committee, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall, Jr. (10 folders), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 17-24, Box 58, Box-folder 1-2)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall, Jr.-Retirement, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Brown, J. Gordon, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Bull, F.W., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Burchard, Charles, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Dean, James W. (4 folders), 1974 (Box 58, Folder 7-10)
  - Harper, Laura Jane, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Harvard, William C., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Hereford, Karl T., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Hill, David E. and Others, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Lacy, M.P., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Lavery, W.E., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Malpass, L.F., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Martin, James E., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Mitchell, H.H., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Ross, D.L., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Skelton, W.E., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Talbot, Richard B., Dean-College of Veterinary Medicine, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Torgersen, P.E., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Wilson, C.T., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Bell, Wilson B., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Boone, J.F., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Burke, C.E., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Butt, A.T., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Evans, E.B., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Gibson Computing Center, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - King, H.P., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Montgomery J.R., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Moseley, F.O., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Nickols, I.E. (2 folders), 1974 (Box 58, Folder 34-35)
  - Nunley, C.F., 1974 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Robertson, R.M., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Rudolph, G.A., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Russell, G.E., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Schiffert, C.W., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Shotts, J.E., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Strother, W.H., and others, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Sterrett, W.M. (2 folders), 1974 (Box 59, Folder 7-8)
  - Wheeler, W.M., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - The Art Commission, Floyd. E. Johnson, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Attorney General-Andrew P. Miller, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts-Joseph F. James, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Department of Treasury, Frank B. Miller Jr., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Division of Budget, John R. McCutcheon, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Executive Order-Governor, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Property Records and Insurance, Stewart R. Moore, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Governor-Mills E. Godwin Jr., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Division of Engineering and Buildings, H.D. Hamner, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Division of Personnel, John W. Garber, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Purchases and Supply, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - State Council of Higher Education (2 folders), 1974 (Box 59, Folder 21-22)
  - State Highway Department (2 folders), 1974 (Box 59, Folder 23-24)
  - A-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Applications, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Appalachian Power Company, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - B-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Blacksburg, Town of, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Blanket Letters, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Budget Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Building Lockup, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Building Dedications, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - C-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Capital Outlay-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Cassell, S.K.-Personal, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Coach, A.D., 1974 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - C and P Telephone Company, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Counseling Center, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Donaldson Brown Center, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - E-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Criterion Studies, Inc, 1974 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Energy Conservation, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Enrollment Projections, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Impact Statements, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - F- Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Fireworks Display, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - First National Bank Exchange, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Founders Day Program, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Frederick County Fruit Grower's Association, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Harder, Martha- Special Academic Program, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Huffman, Stanley, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Health and Safety Committee (2 folders), 1974 (Box 60, Folder 15-16)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - J-Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 18)